https://scientificsearch.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Scientific Search
Find TalentOverviewPharmaceutical & Life SciencesEngineering & ManufacturingInformation TechnologyCPG, Food & BeverageMarket ResearchStaffing OptionsRetained SearchPolicies & GuaranteesJob Order RequestJob SeekersOverviewSearch Available JobsInterviewing TipsSubmit Your ResumeContractorsBenefitsHarassment PolicySafety PolicyPayroll ProceduresTimesheetsAbout UsOur TeamAreas of ExpertiseJoin Our Team/CareersTestimonialsPresident’s LetterRecruiting BlogContact Us Select Page
Privacy Policy Effective date: September 21, 2018Scientific Search (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://scientificsearch.com website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://scientificsearch.comInformation Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPERSONAL DATAWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information (PII) that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberCookies and Usage DataUSAGE DATAWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.TRACKING & COOKIES DATAWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataScientific Search uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Scientific Search will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal RequirementsScientific Search may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Scientific SearchTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enLinks To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: info@scientificsearch.comBy visiting this page on our website: https://scientificsearch.com/privacy
CORPORATE OFFICEScientific Search 100 Larwin Rd Cherry Hill, NJ 08034 856-761-0900 FollowFollowFollow
CompanyHomeAbout UsOur TeamWork at Scientific SearchRecruiting BlogContact Us Recruiting ServicesJob SeekersRecruiting Areas of ExpertisePharma & Life SciencesEngineering & ManufacturingInformation TechnologyMarket Research Subscribe to our quarterly newsletterSuccess! First Name
Email
Subscribe We will not share your email.
Copyright © 2011-2020 Scientific Search. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy | Home | Contact
Website Design/Development by 610 Digital, LLC
×
Joseph PetersPRESIDENT(856) 395-0122joe@scientificsearch.com Follow
Prior to acquiring Scientific Search in 2001, Joe spent 15 years in various engineering, sales, recruiting and management positions.  His education includes a BS in Commerce & Engineering from Drexel University, and an MBA from Temple University.Joe’s career began in engineering as an Applications and Sales Engineer for Environmental Tectonics Corp. After five years, he joined a regional staffing company in 1989, and rose to the role of Vice President of Operations, managing 11 offices and over $20 million in revenue.Under his leadership, Scientific Search began specializing in select industries in an effort to provide high quality staffing and recruiting services. These industries include Pharmaceutical, Biotech, Information Technology, Food & Beverage, Engineering, and Market Research. Joe participates in recruiting for key positions with some of Scientific Search’s strategic clients. He has successfully placed over 200 professionals himself, in addition to the thousands Scientific Search has placed.Joe’s expert leadership has resulted in numerous awards and recognitions. The “Philadelphia Business Journal” named Joe to both their South Jersey and Philadelphia Hall of Fame, as a result of Scientific Search qualifying for Philadelphia’s top 100 fastest growing companies on 5 separate occasions. His contributions also earned Scientific Search recognition as one of the fastest growing companies 2 years running by “The Inc 5,000.”Joe has taken a leadership role in the recruiting and staffing industry and is the past president of the Mid Atlantic Staffing Association (MASA).Fun Fact:Joe enjoys both golf & tennis, especially on Scientific Search’s annual reward and training trips.Testimonials:“I have been working with Scientific Search for over a year, and in a short period of time, Scientific Search has become the first and only choice to our hiring needs. Joe and his staff understand our industry and do whatever it takes to get the job done.”– Human Resources Manager, Chemical Plant“Scientific Search went beyond what I have experienced with other recruiting firms. They worked closely with us identifying qualified candidates from both a skill and cultural standpoint, handled our prescreening process professionally, and helped in conveying our vision.”– Director of Human Resources, Biotechnology Company“You and your staff at Scientific Search have repeatedly exhibited a high level of dedication and responsiveness to me as a client. You have delivered for me even when faced with what would be perceived by others as an impossible time frame. I consider you and your staff an important resource for my company, and have recommended Scientific Search to others in my position.”– President, Pharmaceutical Consulting and Engineering Company
